Guide to the Annette Weiner Papers MC 152
New York University Archives
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Greenwood, Davydd J., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Gruber, Abraham, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Grupper, Samuel M., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Guyer, Jane, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Hanley, Sarah, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7806 7
  - Harvey, David, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Heijboer, C.J., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Henley, Paul, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Herman, Menachem, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hill, Carole, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hischman, Albert O., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Holwitz, Stan, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Honingsberg, Michael, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Howson, Jean, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Huang, Alice, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Huasi, Ivan, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Illuz, Eva, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ingham, John M., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Iteanu, Andre, 1990-1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - James, Wendy, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Jelliffe, Elizabeth H., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Jerico, Susan, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Christopher, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Jonas, Saran, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Kaplan, Flora S., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Karp, Ivan, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Kaufman, David A., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Keane, Webb, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Kennelly, Brian G., undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Kertzer, David, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Kirshenblatt-Gimblet, Barbara, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Knauft, Bruce, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Koeppel, Alfred J., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Kolenda, Pauline, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Kopcke, Gunter, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Kotilainen, Eija-Maija, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Krabbenhoft, Kenneth, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Kriser, David B., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Kryukov, Vassily, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lancaster, Roger, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Langdon, George D. Jr., 1991 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Lee, Richard B., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Leonard, Robert D., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lepani, Charles, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Lepani, Katherine, 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Lindenbaum, Shirley, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Lindstrom, Lamont, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Lindstrom, Marty, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Linnekin, Jocelyn, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Lomnitz, Claudio, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Losche, Diane, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Lubar, Robert, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Lynton, Linda, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - MacMillen, Liz, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Macneil, Denise, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Mandel, Jack S., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Maranhao, Tullio, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Maretski, Tom, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Marrazzi, A., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Marrett, Cora Bagley, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Marx, Emanuel, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Massey, Walter, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Mathews, Thomas F., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - May, Stephanie, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - McAdams, Robert, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - McChesney, Lea S., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Meneley, Anne, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Mielke, Joan Tyler, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Millard, Ann V., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Miller, Linda, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Milligan, James, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Mitchell, Ned, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Mitchell, William, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Moore, Donald A., 1991 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Murrell, Mary, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Myers, Fred, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Napier, David, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Neiburg, Federico, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Nichol, L. W., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Norick, Frank A., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Obbink, Laurie, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Ohnuki-Tierney, Emiko, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Oliva, L. Jay, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Oncology Associates, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Parezo, Nancy, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Peacock, James, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Pearce, Tola, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Penn, Mischa, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Peters, Victoria, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 84A)
  - Pobbi-Asamani, K. O., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Polish Academy of Sciences, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Pomponio, Ali, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Prieto, Eric, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Prischak, Robert W., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Pulford, Mary, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Ram, Haggay, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7814 1
  - Raymo, Robert, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Reilly, Linda Collins, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rejtmar, Dale A., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3A)
  - Renne, Elisha P., 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rice, C. Duncan, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rich, B. Ruby, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Robertson, Dale B., 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Rochell, Carlton, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Rogers, Lorene L., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ronis, Max L., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rosaldo, Renato, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Rosbottom, Ronald, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Rosenthal, Arthur J., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Rouse, Irving, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rudenstine, Neil L., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ruvolo, Maryellen, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - St. Mary's College of Maryland, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Sano, Tochiyuki, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Sass, Louis, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Schaffer, Andrew, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Scheper-Hughes, Nancy, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Schlegel, Alice, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Schneider, David M., 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Schoen, Sharon L., 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Schrift, Alan D., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Schwartz, Douglas, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Scoditti, Giancarlo M. G., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Scupin, Ray, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Selshin, Nina, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Senft, Gunther, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Sennett, Richard, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Shapley, Robert, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Shapiro, Judith, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Sherry, John, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Sherzer, Joel, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Shinn, Beth, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Shokeid, Moshe, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Sibley, Willis E., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Siegal, Bernard J., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Silverman, Sydel, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Skalnik, Peter, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Slichter, Charles P., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Sokol, Herman, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Soviet Anthropology, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Spindler, George, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Steele, Marcy, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Stefanoff, Lisa, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Stewart, Jean, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Stoller, Paul, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Strathern, Marilyn, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Sturtevant, William C., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Swedlund, Alan, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Taylor, Lucien, 1990-1996 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Tedlock, Barbara, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Terrio, Susan, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Thomas, Ashoka, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Thomas, Nicholas, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Trueblood, Marilyn, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Uhl, Sarah, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Valerio, Valeri, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Van der Meer, Annewil, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Velez-Ibanez, Carlos, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Viola, Ray, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 62A)
  - Vrhel, Frantisek, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Vryonis, Speros, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Wade, Nicholas, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Walley, Chris, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Ward, Martha C., 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Washington, Robert O., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Wasserman, Marlie, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Weatherford, Jack, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Weiner, Annette from various..., 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Weiner, James F., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Weingrod, Alex, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Welsch, Rob, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - West, Richard, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - White, Randy, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Wiebe, Robert H., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Wildavsky, Aaron, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Williams, Jason, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Willis, Ellen, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 79A)
  - Willson, Magaret, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Wilson, Thomas H., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Witherspoon, Kimberly, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Wobst, H. Martin, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Wood, Chauncey, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Yamamoto, Matori, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Yerkovich, Sally, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Young, Philip D., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Zamora, Mario D., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Zimmer-Tamakoshi, Laura, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Zimmerman, Francis, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Zorn, Jean, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Zurakowski, Patricia, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Letter from David Wason, 1990 (Box Shared University Archives 024, Folder 5)
- Series II: Teaching
  This series contains materials related to her Teaching.
  - Articles for Core Courses (Levi- Strauss, Radcliffe- Brown, & Weber), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7815 8
  - Bibliographies of Various Experts' List, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1A)
  - Bibliographies (2) - Melanesia (Noted attached), undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bibliographies- Melanesia Ethnography, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2A)
  - Bibliographies- Samoa, undated (Box 8, Folder 2B)
  - Bibliographies- Social Anthropology Core Course, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bibliographies- The Trobriand Islands, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographies- Various, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bibliographies- Various (A-C), undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bibliographies- Various (D-H), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bibliographies- Various (I-O), undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bibliographies- Various (P-Z), undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bibliographies- Various- Untitled Bibliographies, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lecture Notes- Core Courses, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Syllabi from Core Course, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Syllabi from Core Course, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Syllabi from Core Course, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Syllabi from Core Course, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Article on Anthropological Issues (various topics) Alphabetical by subject, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Articles on Kwakiutl Tribe from Various authors (A-E), undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Articles on Kwakiutl Tribe from Various authors (F-Z), undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Anthropology Department- Guidelines for Written Papers, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Journal on Anthropology Positions/ Careers (Various Titles), undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Seminar Papers from 1960s-1970s (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Social& Cultural Core Course: Final Examination, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Article on Incest by various authors (A-E), undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7816 6
  - Article on Incest by various authors (F-M), undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Article on Incest by various authors (N-V), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Article on Incest by various authors (W-Z), undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bibliography on Incest, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Incest Patterns, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (A-C), undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (D), undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (E-F), undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (G), undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (H-K), undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (L-R), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7817 4
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (Scheffler, H. W.), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (Scheffler, H. W.), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (Scheffler, H. W.), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Articles on Kinship by various authors (Schneider- Z), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Articles on Kinship- classical work on Family and Kinship, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Class Syllabi- Kinship Classes, 1975-1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Glossary of Kinship Terminology, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Kinship- Mason Paper- Marriage Theory, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Course Seminar and outline on Anthropology Department, 1972-1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Class Syllabi- Social Anthropology Class, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Class Syllabi- Kinship and Marriage Class, 1976, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Lecture and notes on Incest, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Notes on Kinship Patterns, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Review and Lecture-Sahlins, Marshall: Stone-Age Economics, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bibliography for Social Organization Course, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Kinship- Notes for Papers on 'Social Organization of Nonlinear Societies", 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Kinship- Wilmson Paper at Seminar on African Studies, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Notes and Articles on Theory-'Benedict Chronology", 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7818 2
  - Notes and Articles on Theory-'Boaz", 1938, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Notes and Articles on Theory-'Boaz", 1943 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Notes and Articles on Theory-'Boaz", 1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Notes and Articles on Theory-'Boaz", 1948 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Notes and Articles on Theory-'Boaz" (xerox of 1899 and 1907 notes), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Notes on Theory-'Durkheim, Marx & Smith", undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Theory-'Froyer", undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Notes on Theory-'Kroecer, Steward, and White", undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Articles on Theory-Lee, Richard B., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Notes on Theory-'Levi-Bruhl", undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Notes on Theory-'Levi-Strauss", undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Notes on Theory-'Malinowski", undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Notes on Theory-'Radcliffe-Brown", undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Notes on Theory-'Radcliffe-Brown", undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Articles on Theory- Seligman's reprints, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Notes on Theory- 'Tyler's History Concept", undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Notes on Theory- 'Weber", undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Articles on History- History of Anthropology by various authors (A-C), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7819 0
  - Articles on History- History of Anthropology by various authors (D-E), undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Articles on History- History of Anthropology by various authors (F), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Articles on History- History of Anthropology by various authors (G-K), undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Articles on History- History of Anthropology by various authors (L-M), undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Articles on History- History of Anthropology by various authors (N-Z), undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Articles on History- History of Anthropology, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Articles on History- History of Eugenies, 1968, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Articles on History- Patterns of Culture and Primitive Literature, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7820 8
  - Articles on History- Religious Practices (Malinowski, Siegal, Unamura, and Winch)' xerox of 1913 articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bibliographies on History- History of Anthropology, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Notes and Articles on History- American Anthropology, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Notes and Images on History- 18th 19th Anthropological Practices, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Notes on History- Hallowell's Anthropological Chronology, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Notes on History- History of Anthropology, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Notes on History- History of Anthropological Theory (General), undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Notes on History- History of Anthropology, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Papers on History- Ethnographic Histories (various sources), undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Notes on History- Social Organization of Societies, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Pacific Course Syllabus & Bibliography, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Notes on Pacific-Lecture note #1 & #2, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Notes on Pacific-'G. Batasm- G. Herdt- Cook's Voyage- Baruya notes", undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Notes on Pacific Exchange Lecture (hand written), undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Exchange, Value and Corruption Course: Notes on corruption lecture, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Exchange, Value and Corruption Course: Syllabus and schedule, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Material Culture Course: course outline, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Magic- Articles on Magic& Witch by various authors, 1944-1970s (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7821 6
  - Magic- Articles on Magic& Witch (author unknown), undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Magic- Notes on Magic in Primitive Societies, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Magic- Notes on Witchcraft& Possession by Thomas, Keith, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Magic- Notes on Trobriand Islands: Spells& Ritual, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Magic- Paper on Magic, Religion and Science by Evans- Pritchard, E.E., 1932-1933 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Magic- Papers on Witchcraft and Possession, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Magic- Research Proposal on Magic and Social Interaction, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Religion- Articles on Images, Idols, and Religions Law by various authors (A-F), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Religion- Articles on Images, Idols, and Religions Law by various authors (G), 1945, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Religion- Articles on Images, Idols, and Religions Law by various authors (H), 1960s (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Religion- Articles on Images, Idols, and Religions Law by various authors (I-Z), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Religion- Articles on Images, Idols, and Religions Law (authors unknown), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Ritual- Articles on Elements of Ritual and Human Interaction by various authors (A-S), 1955-1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ritual- Articles on Elements of Ritual and Human Interaction by various authors (T-Z), 1973, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Ritual- Bibliographies for Classes, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Ritual- Journals on Natural History & Anthropology Practices, 1971, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Ritual- Notes on Semiology & Behavior Patterns, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Cargo Cults- Articles on Structure & Function by various authors (A-J), 1956-1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7822 4
  - Cargo Cults- Articles on Structure & Function by various authors (K-Z), 1943, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cargo Cults- Notes on Structure & Operation, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bushmen- Articles on Cultural Patterns (Marshall, Lorna), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Bushmen- Articles on Cultural Patterns (Marshall, Lorna), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bushmen- Articles on Ethnographies Descriptions (general), 1966-1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bushmen- Articles on Kung Culture & Patterns, 1973-1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bushmen- Bibliographies on Ethnographies & Cultural Norms, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bushmen- Notes on Cultural Laws of Tribes, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bushmen- Articles on Kung Culture (personal collection), 1975, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Bushmen- Paper on Kalahari Foragers (Wilmsen & Biesele), undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Series III: Field notes & Field works
  This series contains materials related to her Field Studies. The materials are in either chronological or alphabetical order.
  - Correspondence- Malinowski Letters from Various Correspondents (xerox copies of letters dating from 1850-1938), undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7823 2
  - Correspondence- Malinowski Letters from Various Correspondents, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- Various Professional Courtesy and Request Letters on Trobriand Islands, 1970s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- Milne Bay Correspondences on Various Professional Courtesy, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- Various Personal Cards and Notes, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- Various Professional Courtesy and Request Letters, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- Various Professional Courtesy and Request Letters, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- Letters re Trobriands, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- Various Professional Requests, Awards, Papers, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- Various Personal Cards and Letters- Retirement & Sympathy, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- Pleasant Valley Farm Letters, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-Papua New Guinea- Visa Administrative Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-Papua New Guinea- Visa Administrative Correspondence, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Papua New Guinea- National Statistical Office, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Papua New Guinea- Papua New Guinea Officials, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- Trobriand Islands- Ichioka, Yosuke, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- Trobriand Islands- King, Walter B., 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Trobriand Islands- National Geographic Material, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- Trobriand Islands- Senft, Gunter, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- Trobriand Islands- Wormsley, William E., 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Guatemala- Correspondences on Guatemala, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7824 0
  - Guatemala- Memorandum: Archaeological- Ethnohistorical Research Project of Antigua, Guatemala, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1A)
  - Guatemala- report on Guatemala's Ceramics, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Guatemala- Written Papers on Guatemala Summer 1969 and Photo (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Magic- Articles about Magic and Myths by Various Authors, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Magic- Language and Vocabulary Book I, II, VI, VII, IX, and XI, 1971-1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Magic- Bibliography Notes, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Magic- Magic Drafts from 1970s by Annette Weiner, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Magic- Miscellaneous about Magic, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Papua New Guinea- Election in Kula, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Papua New Guinea- Government and General Literature, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Papua New Guinea- Notebook on 'Sogalin", 1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Papua New Guinea- Photos, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Papua New Guinea- Kasaipwalova, John: Criminal Law...Court Appeal, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Papua New Guinea- Election News and Letters, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Samoa- Correspondence- Beriss, David, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7825 7
  - Samoa- Correspondence- Cain, Horst, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Samoa- Correspondence- Meleisea, Penelope Schoeffel, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Samoa- Correspondence- Pareira, Janet, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Samoa- Correspondence- Ritter, Judith C., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Samoa- Correspondence- Sapolu, Katalaina, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Samoa- Correspondence- Weiner, Annette B., 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Samoa- Donation of Samoa Artifacts by Post, Nathan, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Samoa- Maps, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Samoa- Language & Vocabulary of Samoa by Pritchard (1866), Mead (1930), and others, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Samoa- Language & Vocabulary of Samoa- Book III, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Samoa- Nonumalo Tape Lists & Samoan Vocabulary, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Samoa- Nonumalo, tape 1A, 1B, 2, ie, and Miscellaneous about Tapes, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)